{
    "subject": "resource/Rich_Relations_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/editing",
    "object": "Henry Spitz",
    "human_readable": "The film Rich Relations was edited by Henry Spitz.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9140621423721313,
            "question": "Who edited the film Rich Relations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8929873704910278,
            "question": "Name a film edited by Henry Spitz."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8620065450668335,
            "question": "Is Henry Spitz a film editor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8170571327209473,
            "question": "What is the name of the film that Henry Spitz edited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7420808672904968,
            "question": "Who directed the film Rich Relations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6957022547721863,
            "question": "Has Henry Spitz worked on any other films besides Rich Relations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5396581888198853,
            "question": "When was the film Rich Relations released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45546144247055054,
            "question": "What genre is the film Rich Relations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3645784854888916,
            "question": "What is the profession of Henry Spitz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19615407288074493,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in Rich Relations?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film Rich Relations was edited by Henry Spitz.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3520_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the profession of Henry Spitz?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3520_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Rich Relations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3520_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the film Rich Relations released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3520_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3520_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3520_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3520_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3520_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3520_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3520_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3520_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3520_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3520_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3520_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe document at `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3520/re-ranker-msmarco/62.txt` states under the CAST & CREW section that \"Edited by Henry Spitz\", which supports the triple that the film Rich Relations was edited by Henry Spitz."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}